LÊ THÀNH TRUNG

Intern Pentest Web



Profile

- 🖰 17/04/2000
- Nam
- 0981878713
- ✓ lethanhtrung0x0a@gmail.com
- An Hòa Xã An Thới Đông Cần Giờ HCM
- https://github.com/magnetohvcs

Skill

Specialized skills

Basic knowledge of web attacks: SQL injection, XSS, SSRF, SSTI, XXE Knowledge of languages: Python, Java, PHP, Nodejs, C/C++, Bash script Linux

Soft skills

Team work, good communication and stable research ability

Goal

Desire to become an intern at your company, which allows me to update my knowledge about the latest trends, contributing to my personal development.

Education

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

8/2018 - now

Major: Information Security

Experience

Lab attacks ddos with trin00

4/2021 - 4/2021

Information Security Facility

Role: design and build lab to simulate ddos attack on webserver https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=puix6ngwvnQ

Lab intrusion and privilege escalation

4/2021 - 4/2021

Information Security Facility

Role: design and build a lab to simulate a compromised server and escalate privileges to the root user

Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z9iUylzsdCE

Work

Join the school's Information Security club.

10/2019 - now

Member

Study and support other members of the club

ASEAN student contest on information security 2020 quals

9/2020 - 10/2020

Participant

ASEAN student contest on information security 2021 quals

10/2021 - 10/2021

Participant

Consolation prize

Play CTF on ctftime, rootme, tryhackme, hackthebox

Participant